Welcome to the EGS test server!

Update: Elevator/ramps delay, club door fixed.

Join us on IRC at #egs on irc.lunarnet.org
Or in the forums at http://psumods.co.uk/forums/

See the following pages for a list of features
and known issues.

Note that currently, 'Your Room' sends you to the
club.

-- Essen

KNOWN ISSUES:

When someone connects, everyone resets to facing
one direction, doesn't appear in chairs anymore.
The new person also see everyone standing up.

Players disconnecting don't disappear (ghosts).

JP clients post-sup are not working correctly.






FEATURES

* Login
* Chat, cut-in chat
* Movements, animations, etc.
* Emotes
* Sit, chairs, alternate sitting positions
* Uni cube
* Floor 1-4, club lobbies
